Baskata Orijines Inbuy
Bonjour
Seino
This is Sakurazaka46
After a 13.5 hour flight
I've arrived in Paris!
Yay!
Yay! We're here!
We're here after all! We're going to have fun!
Yay! How's your first time abroad?
First time abroad, how about you?
It's fun, isn't it?
I want to see a little bit of everything.
Yay! Let's take lots of pictures.
Let's take lots of pictures.
I'm good, I'm good. Suddenly everyone is taking pictures.
I'm trying to do it fast, but look, I'm trying to do it fast, but look!
You're not making me do it fast enough!
I can't wait to do it, I can't wait to do it, I can't wait to do it.
I'm going to go eat now.
I'm going out to eat now.
Everyone loves the height of the café. I'm having a little trouble keeping my eyes open.
You're walking! I'm so glad you're walking around town.
I don't like the crow's posture in Paris.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I just have a feeling.
Super.
Ta-da!
Rock on, Mr. Icarus.
What do you think?
Did you find what it says?Did you find anything on it?
No, I haven't seen it yet.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Oh, my God.
That narrows it down.
That's great.
Reach for it.
It's so cute.
They've arrived.
This is the place.
Like this.
There's a line... with a girl.
There was a girl.
Oh, my God.
Ta-da!
Face-palm cooperation.
Bon appétit!
Itadakimasu button for thousands of yen.
Itadakimasu means "Let's have it," indeed.
Check it out... around here.
Merci.
Thank you and
Three colors
Sablulé.
Sablulé
Sablooleh
Ta-da!
What is this?
Chocolate.
Delicious!
Rich and Merci!Thick Merci
Thick Merci
Is it good?
It was delicious!
Eyes on the food
Come out
Face
Difficult
Thank you for watching
Cute
Gentlemen.
Yoo-hoo!
Now.
Chandelier.
Okay. Okay.
I think we're in Paris.
Hey. - Hey.
Wow.
Whoa!
Wow!
I'm kind of loose in the exposure.
You scared me.
Wow! I have goosebumps.
I swear I had a weird look on my face.
Oh my God, wait.
I haven't eaten today. I'm starving.
Oh, look who's here!
What's that smoke?
It's our anniversary.
It's so exciting.It's so exciting.
Oh, my God, it's so much fun.
Don't hit me! Don't hit me!
Don't hit me!
If you hit me like this...
I'm gonna get a little bruise on my shoulder.
My shoulder's gonna go "pareen"!
Oh, my shoulder's gonna go "pareen"!
I knew it!
That's great.
The main gate! Walking toward the main gate
I'm taking a picture of Fu-chan!
Yay! Pho!
Pine trees are so beautiful!
So pretty!
Oh, my God!
What's that?
Taishomon's here!
Shalby Dance?
OK?
He's too happy.
You're all from Sakurazaka's first term, right?
Yes.
How did you know?
I'm finally a member.
Thank you.
I'm in trouble.It's not good.
It's good.
It's good?
Oh, man.
Paliafel.
Yes!
It's starting.
We did it.
Nothing's going well, is it?
Now we're going to Setosawa Mobile Arts.
Yay!
Sakura to Orizincu Inmarie!
It's so good!
Super cute!
It's spinning around!
So cute!
This place is so good.
What about Otenha?
Cute yui chan!
Okay, okay, good, good, good.
It's good.
It's okay, I'm cutting it.
So cute! The road here is so cute!
It's okay, Ten-chan's cute.
Thank you.
Barbie, Barbie, Barbie, Barbie, Barbie, Barbie, Barbie, Barbie, Barbie, Barbie, Barbie.
Barbie
Barbie.
Ooh.Ooh.
Ooh.
Just in time.
Wow.
I got sun class.
I'm going to the island now.
Let's go!
This is Seibu River
Seibu River
It's going to be fun!
Let's have fun!
Let's go!
Wow!
A boat!
Oh, wow.
Want to buy one?
Bye bye!
Meow.
Did anyone notice?
Oh, you noticed.
Thank you.
Oh, thank you
Bye
Thank you Cat Mouse
Rouant Arnette
That's great!
That's great!It's amazing!
Cute cafe
Hello.
The courthouse
It's really stylish.
Cute.
A courthouse.
A real courthouse.
Oh, my God.
That's amazing.
That's so cute.
What's that?
The pink ladle.
It's really cute.
It's so cute.
Bon appétit!
Have a nice day.
It's so bright!
Wow.
Amazing.
Notre Dame lifelt
That's it!
The color of the doves is totally different from Japan's.
So cute!
Oh, it's so cute!
By the way
Cute!
It's cute.
Ms. Benna.Mr. Benna.
Yes, ma'am.
Dove Dove Dove
It's flowing nicely.
It's flowing well.
Something is flowing well
Thank you for your hard work!
Arrival at Chirato-ya!
Wow!
We've arrived at the Chilat Restaurant!
What is this?
It's Chilat bread, right?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, I love it!
Bread!
Bread bread.
What did you do with it?
Oh, Chirato?
It's a quiz.
Strawberry.
Yes, strawberry. I was going to order strawberry now.
I ordered caramel.
I'll have a shake.
I was wondering if you could make me a shake out of these.
I'll have a cherry... cherry.
Cherry. Oh, that's a good idea. Cherry.
I'm excited.
How's it coming?
Here you go.
Wow, thank you.
Delicious.Delicious.
Cute.
Amazing!
Yay!
Shake.
What is it?
Spangos.
Spango-straberry.
Looks so good!
Here it comes!
Yay!
Pretty flowers.
They're all pretty flowers!
See you next time, airs legen
We're going to have ice cream now!
There's a line.
Sylvut.
What's that?
She asked for something... a silbut.
Chilbulé?
What's that?
Strawberry lemon.
Roses and chocolate.
A sheet.
I'll eat.
Bon appétit.
Here you go.
It's good.
Is it good?
Ta-da!
It's an amusement park.It's an amusement park.
I'm off to the amusement park.
People are going to drink.
It's over!
It was long! It's been a long time!
Frozen.
Wow! There are so many flavors!
Delicious!
I'm looking forward to it! I'm looking forward to it!
It's hard.
Yes!
Oh, man! This is it!
This is great!
Bon appétit.
Delicious!
People are less dumbfounded by the pictures
The role
Soaking wet
They are too pampered
It's dazzling.
Is this going to make me thinner?
Dazzling glue
Mr. Hubs, you're going to have a blast in Paris, aren't you?
Yes, ma'am.
Crunchy.
It's not Paris.
There are many hills.
So many hills.
Lots of hills.
GoboGobo
Gobo
We're singing here, too.
They're singing here.
Tokyo
Notebook Kyoto
In Kurkruzee
We have arrived!
Wow.
Mwah.
Mmm.
Mnh-mnh.
Huh? You're going to the asshole?
We collaborated with Ricoh Rat, right?
Ha-ha-ha.
You whistle really well.
You do?
You're a good whistler.
RICOH Lert collaboration.
Thank you very much for your time.
We look forward to seeing you again next time.
I have something to tell you.
See you soon!
That's great.
What's that written in Euros?
I don't understand.
Okay, bye.
Oh!oh! (expression of surprise)
Cute.
I'm curious
Revlon
LeBron, you look good in this.
This one?
Yeah, I like it.
It's pretty.
I like it.
It's so cute.
Smells so good.
It smells so good.
Isn't that Klon?
It's so Kira-ish.
My mom loves pandas.
I'll buy some for her.
Mom loves pandas.
It's so cute.
It's for me.
Here's one for you, doggy.
I'd like to find a matching stuffed animal
I'd like to find a matching stuffed animal.
I'd like to match them.
He's cute, too.
He's adorable.
Sure, I'll take this one.
I've got three in my hand.
For sure.
Limited
Sideways.
I'm buying for my dog.I'm buying for my dog.
For your dog.
Open it.
Isn't it super cute?
It's so cute.
Okay, I got it.
Mana.
Oh, hey.
Shall we go to the store?
Let's go to the store.
Let's go to the store
Cherry blossoms
Hey, there are a lot of magnets.
Sakura pose
Cute, cute.
I want a magnet.
Oh, don't put that thing on.
Onigiya.
Chica-chan's magnet, no way!
She seems to like magnets.
It's so cute!
I want this one
I want this one, this one
It's so cute!
Where would you put it?
It's too cute.
Is this it?
Yeah, it's cute.
No, thank you.Very well.
Good night.
He's so cute.
Eh, cute.
Cute.
Amazing.
It's too cute.
Oh, this is it.
It's so cute.
I'm so happy.
I bought it!
The most famous one.
This chocolate...
Ta-da!
I bought this tablet!
It's on YouTube like this.
Oh my god, it blurs over here!
It's so beautiful.
What do you think?
Yeah, it's really beautiful.
This is the old series.
This is the middle one.
I'm so impressed.
That's amazing.
The one with the wide eyes.
Hey, I opened my eyes.
Amazing, really amazing
Cairo.
Cairo.Cairo.
Well, I guess we're done then.
Bye-bye.
Lammont.
Yay.
Paris.
What a dorky-looking thing.
Merci. Delicious. Delightful. Fun. Merci. Paris.
Because it makes Paris look like it's slipping
Paris.
Okay, thank you.